<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Green Crop App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be 8 or more than 8 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_weather">Weather</string>

    <string name="faq">
       1. Where do I get Android Studio? \n

Android Studio is available for download at the developer.android.com site.\n\n\n

2. Is Android Studio a fork of IntelliJ IDEA?\n

No. Android Studio and the Android plugin for IntelliJ IDEA are built from
        the same code, and all of the changes in Android Studio are, and will continue to be,
        available in IntelliJ IDEA releases.\n\n\n

3. When can I get the Android Studio features in IntelliJ IDEA?\n

The EAP of IntelliJ IDEA 13, which includes all of the Android Studio features
        except for the redesigned new project wizard and the App Engine cloud endpoints
        integration, is available now. The remaining features are going to be integrated in the coming weeks.\n\n\n

4. Will the new features of Android Studio be available for users of IntelliJ IDEA 12?\n

No. The new features (especially the Gradle support) depend on the major changes that were done in the version
        13 platform, and we do not have any plans to backport them.\n\n\n

5. If I’m already a user of IntelliJ IDEA, do I need to switch to Android Studio for Android development?\n

No. Android Studio is focused specifically on Android development and provides streamlined environment and project
        setup, but otherwise all of its features are available in IntelliJ IDEA.\n\n\n

6. If I rely on features that are only available in IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate (such as additional version control plugins), will I be able to use Android Studio?\n

No, these additional features will not be available in Android Studio. You should continue using IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate.\n\n\n

7. Are Android Studio projects compatible with IntelliJ IDEA?\n

Yes, the two IDEs use the same project format.\n\n\n

8. Is it planned to support NDK development in Android Studio or IntelliJ IDEA?\n

We have recently announced that we’re starting work on an IDE for C++, and we plan to eventually support NDK development as part of that effort. As for NDK development support in Android Studio, Google hasn’t announced anything so far.\n\n\n

9. Where do I report bugs?\n

If you’re using Android Studio, please report bugs to the AOSP issue tracker. IntelliJ IDEA issues, as before, should be reported through YouTrack."

    </string>

    <string-array name="type">
        <item>Fruits</item>
        <item>Vegitables</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>